[quiet, tense music playing]
[Josh, anxiously] Oh man.
It's not too bad.
I'll fix it in a couple of days.
But it begs the question, why should I?
Why were you in a car accident?
Why is this a secret?
I can't tell you.
It's not because I don't want to,
it's just…
It's not mine to tell.
-Are you safe?
-Yes.
Is he in trouble?
He will be
if anyone finds out about this accident.
-Are you asking me for help or is he?
-Cam, I am.
And I wouldn't be asking you
if it wasn't important.
But you don't owe me anything.
Kind of do.
I'll take care of it.
[Teagan whispers] Thank you.
But next time,
I'm not bailing out your shitty boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend.
No, I'm just a shitty friend.
Cam, whatever it costs, I'll cover it.
It's a favor for Teagan.
Right, well…
I won't forget this.
[intriguing music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[high-energy music playing]
And legs!
Come on, push! Last practice
before the Haverford Cup, come on!
Let's go!
This race is the big one.
Way to bring it, Josh. Come on!
-Great, keep it high, slow into slings.
-[Lana] Great job, boys.
[Hayden] Good hustle.
Man, practice today was sick.
Josh kept the ratio tight.
Nice work, guys.
Looking good out there, everyone.
Well done.
Josh, keep it up.
You're earning your keep.
And perfect time to bring your A game,
because Easton only hosts
the Haverford Cup once every five years.
-You think we have a chance?
-[Hayden] Not gonna sugarcoat it.
Competition's gonna be brutal.
Westvale, Vic City, Claremont,
only the best of the best.
-But who won at the Head of the Laurence?
-[team] We did.
Who won at the Head of the Laurence?
-[louder] We did!
-Damn right.
-And was it a fluke?
-No!
No! And now,
now you have a shot
at medaling at the Haverford Cup.
So go get changed and let's kick some ass
out on the water tomorrow.
Quaid, take us out, big man!
[imitating air horn]
[all cheering]
Okay, there's five boats in our heat,
so if we beat two, we could get bronze.
Except everyone we're up against
has already taken the cup home before.
What's going on?
Baloo says Josh has something to tell us.
[tense music playing]
Well, what is it?
I'm the reason we lost
the Head of the Harbor regatta.
I sabotaged the oar.
What the hell?
-What?
-You made us lose? Why?
[Perry] How could you do that?
[Noah] You lied to us?
[Baloo] Yeah, and he was gonna keep lying.
[Noah] Well, answer us.
He choked.
You're right.
I sabotaged my own oar
to get out of the race.
So what about Baloo's Westvale boyfriend?
No, Logan had nothing to do with it.
I let him take the blame
because I was a coward.
So you got scared and bailed.
Is that gonna happen again tomorrow?
No.
Why should we believe that?
Guys, you need somebody you can count on.
Now, all you gotta do
is tell Coach that you want me in stroke.
Guys, look,
I know trusting me after what I did
is a big ask,
but I can get us to the podium.
Look, Josh messed up,
but practice today was phenomenal.
He's our best shot at medaling.
I can't row for him.
He owned up to it.
That's gotta count for something.
Now, Ryder was stroke when we won.
Teagan won that race.
But it was a winning boat.
Okay, well, you're the tiebreaker, Cam.
Who gets your vote?
Neither of you.
I'm gonna sit this one out, thanks.
[Teagan] Cam.
Didn't think you had it in you.
To own it like that.
Me neither. I'm really sorry, Baloo.
And I'm gonna DM Logan everything
and tell him what happened.
Still not getting my vote.
Fair.
[melancholy music playing]
[vehicle approaching]
[car door opens]
-Juliet.
-I was just seeing if Teagan was home.
-I'll head out.
-Hey.
Are you okay?
My mom canceled
my flight home for Christmas.
She thinks it's better
I stay until spring break.
-Why?
-She didn't say.
I burn a car, they send a new one.
I fake my own kidnapping,
they send an extraction team.
When will they ever just send themselves?
There is only one thing left to do.
Emancipate.
Or maybe just talk to them.
-Or--
-I need to get a job and a place to stay.
And… something else.
I got bored of the AI summary.
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
[Ella] Richard Regis?
[Richard] Hi, Ella. Can we talk?
As you know, my father, Viktor,
is president of Easton's rowing committee.
He's hosting
the Haverford Cup viewing party tomorrow.
It's a very important gathering,
and our party planner just quit.
Not interested.
Wait, let's hear him out.
[intriguing music playing]
Viktor mentioned
the party you threw for Josh.
-The one you fired me from.
-He wants you to take over.
Hm.
I'll make it worth your while.
How much do you make
at the Crab Shack in a year? 50K?
Surprisingly accurate
for someone wearing an ascot.
I'll double it. For one day's work.
What about tripling it
and adding a hospitality coordinator?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
The hospitality coordinator.
-Huh.
-Well?
Done.
[door closes]
-What?
-Looks like we got a job.
Should've seen practice this morning.
I think you're gonna be very happy
at the race tomorrow.
Well, good to hear it.
I don't wanna jinx it,
but there might be a medal in our future.
[laughs]
-Everything all right?
-No.
The Cambridge Racing Committee
conducted a full inspection of the erg
that Teagan and Cam raced on last week.
-And what'd they find?
-Blister tape in the flywheel.
Okay, well, most rowers use blister tape
to protect their hands.
-I can see how some'd get in the rigging.
-It wasn't an accident.
Meaning?
The machine was tampered with.
And after the equipment check,
the only people who came near that
particular machine were Teagan and Cam.
That's a very serious accusation.
Yes, it is.
Since it only affected our rowers,
I was able to convince the committee
to let us deal with it internally.
But you need to find out
whether it was Teagan or Cam
who tampered with the machine.
And pull them from the boat.
[tense music playing]
You cannot ask me to do that.
I want to win as much as anyone.
But if the committee finds out
that we did not deal with this properly,
Easton will be barred from rowing.
[gloomy music playing]
[sinister music playing]
-[quietly] Dad?
-Hi, Teagan.
How are you here?
I wanted to see you row.
I hear you're a coxswain now.
Let's talk.
After I found out the money was misspent,
I was trying to make everything right.
But then the FBI got wind,
and I ran out of time.
So you left.
-I thought about you every day.
-That doesn't make it better.
That just means that you decided every day
not to be here with us.
I wasn't just running away.
-I was trying to fix things.
-Fix things? Gosh.
I have this now.
It's evidence of everything that we did.
I can sell this for enough money
to set you and your mom up properly.
I don't want that.
You and your mom are both so stubborn,
you know that?
Why won't you two take the money?
I'm trying to help you.
Hold on, what do you mean? Did you see…
Did you see Mom?
Mom knew you were here,
and she didn't tell me?
She didn't want you to get hurt.
Don't be mad at her.
I can't believe this.
I'm gonna be late. I have to go.
Wait, Teag. If I'd stayed, the FBI
would've put me in prison for 20 years--
At least I would've known where you were!
Okay? I could've talked to you!
Don't you get it?
There's only ever been one person
who has kept my dad away,
and that's you!
[upbeat, rousing music playing]
[announcer] All rowers to the docks.
The race will be starting shortly.
Rowing is such an exciting sport.
Have you ever thought about
expanding Easton's rowing program?
Well, we'd love to,
but it's always a challenge
to find enough interest or funding.
It's funny you say that.
This is definitely
the fanciest I've ever looked
to watch a high school sporting event.
Apparently it's tradition
at the Haverford Cup.
You dress like you're going
to the Kentucky Derby.
This one, circulate appetizers. This one,
keep the charcuterie board loaded.
This one, champagne.
Keep it flowing, like the Mississippi.
You're a natural.
-I've got dictator energy.
-[Ella giggles]
[Noah] Just let it go.
We have to race in 20 minutes.
We can't get in the boat
until there's a majority.
You guys seriously wanna row for Josh?
-We do.
-I do.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you on the tarmac?
Are you, Noah, or Perry
gonna switch sides?
You're all still fighting about this?
Guys, come on.
We actually have a shot at medaling.
We're not tanking this opportunity
because of some stupid team spat.
Josh screwed the team,
so the team gets to decide
whether or not to row for him.
Stroke seat is Coach's choice.
Except if everyone
refuses to row for someone.
There's nothing he can do.
Fine.
Then let's get a decision. Cam, over here.
She seems mad.
-What is going on with you?
-A lot of family stuff.
This team is the only thing
that makes sense in my life.
I don't need this bullshit.
Who is it gonna be, Cam?
Teagan, there are no good options.
You really want me to choose between
the one who bribed me or sabotaged me?
Yes. Yes, I do. Because guess what?
If you wanna be a leader,
this is what leadership looks like.
Sometimes all you have are bad options,
and you have to make a choice.
Fine.
[suspenseful music playing]
It's Josh.
We good?
I guess the crew has spoken.
[Crabcatcher clears throat]
Teagan, Cam. My office.
Hey, Ryder.
You win some, you lose some.
I wanna win them all.
Are we really gonna keep competing
for the rest of our lives?
I didn't make the rules.
Come on, if you had
a heart attack tomorrow,
do you think stroke seat
would be the thing that matters?
-Probably not to you since you're in it.
-It doesn't actually matter.
Right. Like you'd ever give up stroke.
-We used to be friends.
-You mean you used to have a sidekick.
Hey. What can I do to make things right?
You wanna be friends?
Give me stroke seat.
[sinister music playing]
You know you don't deserve it.
You are not the best man for the job.
You know it.
There. Twenty percent less ugly.
You're not one of my servers.
Do I know you? You seem familiar.
I'm actually looking for someone.
-David.
-Hey, El.
Oh, yeah, you're Teagan's outlaw dad.
Picture of you on the news is fire,
by the way.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to watch Teagan row.
But the FBI tracked me down.
So you came here? Oh, my God.
Ella, I'm sorry.
I wouldn't be here if I didn't need help.
If I can just stay out of sight
until the regatta's over,
I can leave with the crowd.
I can't help you, David.
So what, are you just gonna turn me in?
-I don't know.
-Hang on, he's Teagan's dad.
Is he a bit of a disaster? Yes.
Hugely embarrassing? Also yes.
But he is here.
He risked everything
because he wanted to see his daughter.
He showed up.
Which is more than I can say
for some parents.
Put this on, keep your head down,
and if you wanna be useful,
wash some dishes.
Thank you, Ella.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for Teagan.
"A disaster" and "hugely embarrassing"?
Own it.
The racing committee found tape
deliberately fed into the drive chain.
Who was it?
-It was me.
-No! It…
-Okay, but I--
I… I tampered with the erg.
I used black blister tape, and I did it
knowing it would disqualify our scores.
Teagan, why would you do that?
I can't answer that. And neither can Cam.
[sighs]
Thank you for your honesty.
You're out of the boat.
-[Cam] But Coach, you can't--
-[Hayden] I don't have a choice.
I'm gonna have to pull up a junior cox.
Cam, just go gather the rest of the crew.
Let me be the one to tell them.
Okay.
Coach, I'm…
I'm… I'm sorry.
So am I.
[melancholy music playing]
[exhales]
[footsteps approaching]
Teagan, what's going on?
I need to talk to you guys.
Um…
I messed up.
I violated one of the rules
of the rowing committee, and…
I need to withdraw from the race.
What?
You're not coxing?
No.
There's gonna be a cox
from the junior team.
-They're gonna lead you out on the water.
-[Baloo] No, you're not leaving.
-You can't.
-[rower] This isn't fair.
We're gonna lose.
You guys don't need me.
You only need each other.
I'm sorry I let you guys down.
So, uh…
[clears throat]
Thank you, guys, really.
I won't do it.
I won't row. Not without you.
Cam.
If she's out, I'm out.
[quiet, determined music playing]
I'm with him.
It's not the same boat without you.
I've got you, Big Tea.
I'd rather lose with you
than win without you.
"O Coxswain! My Coxswain!"
[laughs and sobs]
No cinephiles?
Dude. Dead Poets Society.
[Teagan laughs]
Medals are ugly, anyway.
We both know I never would've
come this far without you.
Just so I'm clear,
you all refuse to race
without Teagan as your coxswain.
After all the hard work you put in
and being this close to a podium,
you'd throw it all away.
Teagan.
You're up.
What?
So I'm back in the… in the boat?
You deserve to be there with your team.
You faced your consequences.
I'll face mine.
-Let's go!
-[all cheering]
Okay, let's go win a race!
-Let's go!
Wow.
Hey. How are you?
Oh! Yes.
Ryder's been speaking
with the junior national scout.
It looks like
there's a place for him next year.
Excellent.
Dad. Karina.
How are the relocation plans
to Rotterdam coming along?
There's more pressing things to focus on,
like Ryder's winter training plans.
Dad, this is Ella,
our fabulous party planner,
as you requested.
Good job, you tracked her down.
Wonderful party.
Thank you. Best place to watch the race
is right over there.
Where's Imogen?
She's on a soul-searching tour
around the world.
We haven't been the same
since Josh's birthday.
Something tells me
you have something to do with that.
No.
I just told her to see people
for who they really are.
There are binoculars on the table
to help see the race.
[Announcer] Welcome, rowers.
Teams for race four,
make your way to the starting line.
[Josh] Yo, Cam. You got a sec?
Yeah. What's up?
Switch seats with me.
What?
Why?
Because. It should be you.
You should lead the team.
I'll follow you.
[inspiring music playing]
All right, Easton.
Hands on.
Up to shoulders.
Walk it forward.
Everyone, Easton's race is about to begin.
Come on over.
I didn't think you were into rowing,
but I suppose you must be a WAG now.
Wives and girlfriends.
-I saw you with Perry.
-I'm neither wife nor girlfriend.
Rumor has it neither are you.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for my brother
and for the love of the sport.
[Hayden] Easton, huddle up.
First time at the Haverford in ten years.
Here's what's in front of you.
Claremont. Haven't lost a race all year.
They'll set the pace.
Westvale. They're beasts,
but we've beat them before,
and we can beat them again.
Roxbury's next to you. They're fast.
An overtake will not be easy.
Then there's Vic City. Take them down,
and we got a chance at a medal.
-Ready?
-[all] Easton!
[Lana] All right, let's go.
[Teagan] Rowing to race position.
Wait, Cam and Teagan are both on the boat?
[announcer] Attention all rowers
for Westvale, Claremont,
Easton Prep, Vic City, and Roxbury.
-Stand by.
-[Viktor] Josh in seven and Ryder in six.
Two chances at stroke and two strikeouts.
I thought one of you wouldn't screw it up.
Yet, here you both are.
[announcer] Starting positions.
[Teagan] Okay, Cam. Technique first.
Next, 20 to sprint, then settle.
First push on my call.
Aye-aye.
Time to shine.
["Set It on Fire" by ANOTR playing]
[exhales]
Attention…
♪ Set it on fire, I said set it ♪
-Row!
-[horn blowing]
Three-quarter! Three-quarter!
Full! Full!
[cheering and yelling]
Long and strong!
[Hayden] We're last.
[Teagan] Easton, don't let it get to you.
Focus on technique. Cam, keep 'em steady.
[Claremont cox] All right,
let's take up the rate. Push!
Claremont is off like a rocket.
Predictable.
They've been untouchable all season.
♪ I said set it on fire
Set, set it on fire ♪
♪ Set it on fire ♪
[Teagan] Ignore Claremont.
Stick to the plan.
♪ Set it on fire ♪
Time to bring the heat.
Westvale's in second.
Roxbury and Vic City
are only two seats away.
In two. One…
Two!
♪ Set, set, I said set it on fire
I said set… ♪
[Roxbury cox]
Easton's on us. Roxbury, pick it up!
[Vic City cox] Vic City.
Quick catches for five strokes.
One.
Two.
-Three.
-[oarlock clatters]
No!
-[crowd exclaims]
-They just caught a crab.
No way they're gonna catch up now.
[Ella laughs]
[feisty music playing]
[Teagan] Four teams left,
three medals. Let's get ours!
We are at a 34.
Cam, I need a 36 to close the gap.
After two…
One.
Two!
Punch it!
Whoa! Whoa! We're off-balance!
They're rushing the catch.
Don't rush the slide, trust the rhythm.
Josh, nice picking it up.
Bow pair, killing it.
Yeah! We're moving now!
I'm on Roxbury's stern.
Oh my God. They're closing in on Roxbury.
We have a shot at third!
[Teagan] Easton, we can take this.
Power ten.
-[Roxbury cox] They're passing us now!
-Now! Send it!
-Show me what you got.
-[Roxbury cox] Keep it up. Push. Push it!
-Do it! Come on!
-[Roxbury cox] Do it! Come on!
-Come on, Roxbury. Two!
-[Teagan] Keep pushing. Come on!
Yeah! Third's ours! Whoo!
A-ha! We're in third!
[squeals] We're in third!
We're excited for third.
[Teagan] Don't get cocky.
Job's not done. Keep the power up.
[rower] Westvale!
-They're gaining on Westvale.
-Keep the rate up, Teagan.
Westvale's just ahead. Take it up to a 38.
We can shut them up here.
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Go hard, we're moving now.
[Westvale cox] Westvale.
We're not losing to Easton. Crank it.
[cheering]
Switch. Switch.
Come on! Keep it together!
Engine room, stay with me!
I know it's the pain cave,
but listen to me.
You've got a lot left in you.
Dig deep! Dig deep!
Do it like it's your last time!
Come on. You got this!
[cox] Drive!
[Teagan] We're right next to them,
empty the tank!
[cox] Push! Push!
Go, Teagan!
Come on, Ryder!
Let's go, Josh!
Go, Bronson!
Who's Bronson?
That's Baloo.
Baloo is Bronson?
I thought they were two different guys.
-Push through! Yeah! Then go!
-[cox] Push!
-Push!
-[Teagan] Hear that?
Claremont just finished.
Come on, Easton. Hit these last strokes!
-[cox] This is it! Sprint! Sprint! Sprint!
-[Teagan] Send! Send! Send!
[all cheering and yelling]
They did it!
-They're in second spot.
-Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-Power ten, guys! Let's go!
-Let's go, boys! Let's go!
[Teagan] Come on, guys, give it your all!
You're almost there!
-[cox] Drive!
-[Teagan] Take us home, guys. Let's go!
Go!
-[horn blows]
-Yeah!
[crowd cheering]
[all yelling and cheering]
-Let's go! Let's go!
-Let's go!
[all cheering]
Oh my God!
-Yes!
-Silver, incredible!
Yeah!
[victorious music playing]
We medaled!
[celebrating continues]
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
[Lana laughing]
[laughing]
[Teagan] Let's go! Whoo! Whoo!
-Yes!
-Yeah!
-Whoo!
Yeah!
Heavier than I thought.
Silver's pretty hypoallergenic.
Okay, they're actually pretty cute.
I'm never letting you go.
-First of many.
-[team] Yeah!
Come on!
Yeah, not bad. Next stop, gold.
-Yeah!
-Is this how you wanted to go out?
-It's better than I imagined.
Here. Try it on.
Oh, yeah. That looks pretty good to me.
[laughing]
-Yo! Whoa, come on, let's go!
-Whoa! What? Hey!
[all cheering]
Okay, wait, hold on.
Wait, where's Coach? Where's Coach?
-Coach!
-Come on!
-Get in here!
-Okay.
[Teagan] Okay. Okay, okay.
-Okay. Eagle pride!
-[team] Eagle pride!
[laughing]
-Hey.
Uh…
I should have trusted you.
And you have every right to say no, but…
-If you ever want to hang out again…
-Just…
[rowers murmuring] Whoa…
[Perry laughs]
Does that answer your question?
[all cheering]
Let's go.
Cam. Can I talk to you?
Yeah. What's up, Coach?
I owe you an apology.
For what?
I told you Easton wouldn't row
for townies like us.
I brought my own baggage into it,
and I shouldn't have.
I was wrong.
But I'm so glad that I was wrong
because you killed it out there today.
I'm proud of you, man.
Thanks, Coach.
Ah.
Incoming.
Hey, it's nice to see Easton
end its losing streak.
Silver. Not the worst.
I'll be training in Florida
over the winter season,
so I'll be ready for next year.
And you, Josh?
[tense music playing]
Um…
Not for me. That was my last race.
I beg your pardon?
I have a heart condition.
Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy. It's serious.
I wanted to carry on the family tradition,
but I can't.
I'm not gonna row anymore.
[Viktor] I'm sorry to hear that.
I wish you better health.
Unfortunately, such a serious condition
is a risk,
and will affect our company's plans.
I understand.
I don't think we heard you right…
Dad.
I think what you meant to say is,
"We love you, Josh,
and we will do whatever it takes
to get you
the best medical care possible."
-[Viktor] Excuse me?
-[Richard] You heard me.
Josh isn't your heir. He's my son.
All right.
Well, I'll let you
get back to your family time.
Karina.
Ryder.
I'd love to hear more
about your winter plans.
Sorry, man.
-He didn't like that.
-Is that bad?
Yes.
But I don't care.
[emotional music playing]
Are you okay? Can they treat it?
Yeah. With surgery.
But it's a pretty rough recovery.
We can deal with rough.
I love you.
I love you too, Dad.
Let's go call your mom.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Congratulations! First medal in ten years.
Yeah. The crew did good.
Have you seen Teagan?
Ah. Right over there.
Is everything okay?
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry. My… My life is so complicated.
Well, I'll be here when it's not.
Hey, honey, congratulations!
-I need to talk to you.
-Okay, well, I don't want to talk to you.
You lied to me about Dad,
and you're keeping things from me.
Yes. He's here,
and I'm hiding him from the FBI.
What? Mom!
This is why
I don't want to tell you things.
Okay, what do we do?
Are we gonna get in trouble?
-[Ella] How bad is aiding and abetting?
-[Teagan] Pretty bad!
Well, whatever, honey.
We'll figure it out.
Teag, you were incredible out there.
Dad, okay, you can't be here.
You gotta go. What if somebody sees you?
Maybe it's time they do.
I don't want you to wonder
where I am anymore.
I'm going to turn myself in.
You're sure?
I'm sure.
Listen, Teag,
I know you're upset at your mom,
but she was just protecting you
from my mess.
She's built a great life for you,
and she did it with less than nothing.
She's pretty amazing.
-[agent] Got eyes on the suspect.
-It's time to go.
[Ella sighs]
[agent] Mr. Tao. You need to come with us.
Exciting day for Easton.
Hey, we got on the podium,
just like you wanted.
Yes.
I couldn't help but notice
that both Teagan and Cam were in the boat.
Were you not able to find out
who the responsible party was?
I was.
But ultimately, as head coach of the team,
I decided that the responsibility
for their actions lies with me.
I see.
Then I don't have much choice,
Coach Hayden.
You're fired.
[somber music playing]
-Hey.
I heard about your dad. You okay?
No.
But, uh… you know,
me and my mom will figure it out.
How'd things go with your family?
Surprisingly not terrible.
Though we might be poor soon.
Poor for us.
Feel free to hit me up for tips
on surviving your downfall.
Will do.
[laughs]
["Syncing" by Miss Grit playing]
Listen.
It's been a really hard time,
and you've been there for me.
You've seen me at my worst.
-Yeah, daily.
-Yeah, well…
You've never seen me at my best.
I'm working on it.
What, you're building a better Josh?
Yeah. And I'm hoping
when you meet that guy,
you'll give him a second chance.
Okay.
See you around.
If I don't die on the operating table.
[Josh laughs]
♪ But nothing stayed
Right where I left it ♪
♪ I'm starting to move… ♪
Just a few more loads.
What should we do with the straw hats?
-Burn them?
-Thanks for today.
What are you gonna do
with the money from this party?
Pay Teagan's tuition.
Okay, after that boring thing,
you should think about
what you wanna do for yourself.
Be selfish.
You're a good kid. You know that?
What an awful thing to say to someone.
[song continues]
[woman] Juliet.
Mom?
Hey, Coxie.
Hey, stroke seat.
["Focus Is Power" by Self Esteem playing]
Been a day.
Yeah, certainly has.
Can't say I imagined this
when you hit me with your bike.
You hit me.
♪ Don't be too loud or too quiet ♪
♪ But I got all this fight ♪
♪ And now I see it clear
With every passing of each year ♪
♪ I deserve to be here ♪
[Lana] Hey, Teagan, are you in here?
I wanna talk to you.
Yeah, I am over here.
-[Cam] I'll go.
-Okay.
Night, Coach.
[Teagan] What's up?
Do you hear that?
It's the sound of your wish coming true.
-My wish?
-I spoke to Cabrera this morning.
Apparently there's a group of girls that
have shown interest in a girls' team,
and they're backed by a wealthy donor.
Congrats, Teagan.
Come spring, you're back in a boat.
What? Oh my God, that's so amazing.
-Thank you so much. I--
-Hey, don't thank me.
Thank the Garner Foundation.
["Fade Away" by Girl Tones playing]
What?
Hey, babe.
I can't wait to be crewmates.
It looks like you row for me now.
♪ Fade ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ Altercation
No motivation ♪
♪ Oh no, it's too complicated ♪
♪ I'm jaded
I'm so frustrated ♪
♪ I'm losing my patience ♪
♪ You always seem to bother me ♪
♪ You deny your immaturity ♪
♪ And as the waves build and break ♪
♪ I'm owed an apology ♪
♪ Fade ♪
♪ Away ♪
[song ends]